const queryList = [
  {
    "question": "What is the eligibility criteria for participating in Icon Coderz?",
    "answer": "The competition is open to all college students, regardless of their institution. The eligibility is divided into two levels:\n\nBeginner Level: For 1st and 2nd-year students.\nExpert Level: For 3rd and 4th-year students."
  },
  
  {
    question:
      "How do I register for the competition?",
    answer:
      "Registration details will be shared on the official event website. Participants typically need to fill out a registration form and submit it before the deadline.",
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of problems will be included in the competition?",
    answer:
      "The competition will feature coding problems that test your problem-solving and algorithmic skills. The problems will range from basic programming concepts to more advanced topics like data structures, algorithms, and computational thinking. ",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I participate as an individual or do I need a team?",
    answer:
      "Icon Coderz is usually an individual competition. Participants will be required to solve problems on their own, showcasing their individual programming and problem-solving skills.",
  },
  {
    question: "What programming languages are allowed in the competition?",
    answer:
      "Common programming languages like C, C++, Java, Python, and others are typically allowed. Specific details regarding language support will be provided in the competition guidelines. Make sure to review the rules before starting the contest to confirm which languages are permitted.",
  },
  {
    question: "Will there be certificates for participation?",
    answer: `
   Yes, participants will receive certificates for their participation in Icon Coderz. Additionally, top performers may receive special recognition or awards based on their performance in the competition.
    `,
  },
  {
    question: "Will there be any practice rounds or mock contests before the actual competition?",
    answer:
      "There will not be any official practice rounds or mock contests before the actual competition. However, participants are encouraged to practice on their own using online coding platforms to prepare for the event. Keep an eye on announcements for any additional resources or updates.",
  },
  {
    question: "How will the winners be determined?",
    answer:
      "Winners will be determined based on the leaderboard results",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the communication channels for participants to reach out to the organizing team?",
    answer: `
Participants can reach out for any inquiries via email at srkrcodingclub@gmail.com. Alternatively, they can contact us directly by phone:
- P.Yogendra: +91 9492100941
- CH Likitha: +91 8688545819
- P.Ankith: +91 9100579797
- S Harshavardhan: +91 9703663860

Feel free to reach out, and we're here to help you with any questions or concerns you might have.
`,
  },
  {
    question:"Are there any social media or online platforms where participants can follow updates about the event?",
    answer:"Yes, you can follow our Instagram handle for event updates: https://www.instagram.com/srkr_coding_club?igsh=MTVycDY4cGs3d3I0ZA==",
  },
  {
    question:"Is there a registration fee for participating?",
    answer:"The registration fee for participating in Icon Coderz is ₹100. However, there is a 50% discount for SRKR Coding Club affiliates.",
  },
  {
    question:"Can I participate in both levels if I'm eligible?",
    answer:"No, you can only participate in one level based on your year of study. If you're in the 1st or 2nd year, you must participate in the Beginner Level, and if you're in the 3rd or 4th year, you must compete in the Expert Level.",
  },
];

export default queryList;
